Muter, Linco. The exciting couple.
Yes, yes, yes.
We've started the first run of "Exciting Couple.
Well, it's kind of started, but first of all, let me tell you about the exciting couple.
First of all, her name is Mutter, and this is Linco. She's my girlfriend.
I'm embarrassed to say she's my girlfriend.
So here's how we met. We met at a high school reunion.
And we kinda got together.
We both like youtube.
I recently told her we wanted to do a couples youtuber thing, and she was like...
No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no.
No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no.
This video is a memorial to our future children.
Stop it!
I'm doing this for that reason.
Today is the first one, so...
I'm going to go out on a limb here.
I came to E Beans
We're here at Rear Garden!
Yay!
Ta-da!
Rinko's favorite crab!
There are a lot of crabs, so I'm going to order a little bit more!
Ready, set, go!
Subscribe to our channel!
azakane!
Canny.
Okay, I'll do it, please.
Oh, sorry, sorry, it was raw.
Ha-ha-ha, that's funny.
It was raw. Oh, my God.
You're funny.
It was raw. It was kind of raw.
It looked so good, I thought I'd try it.
To the excited listeners who regularly watch the Exciting Couple channel
I feel I owe you an apology this time, and I'm shooting this video!
The other day, in the beer garden video.
I apologize for the fact that I tried to eat the samgyeopsal raw in the beer garden video the other day.
Eating it raw is a very dangerous thing to do.
It is a very dangerous thing to do, and I regret that I shouldn't have done it.
I hope that this will not happen again in the future.
And I'm sorry that I betrayed all the excited listeners who are watching this video.
We both regretted it very much.
In order to prevent such a thing from happening in the future
We will discuss this matter thoroughly and
We will continue to take our videos seriously.
Thank you for your continued support!
Hey!
He said it's always the same.
It's too spicy.
No, it's a little bit apple.
It's like I'm being fed to you.
It's 100 times better.
Oh, good.
Shall I put some on?
That's funny.
This is a little embarrassing.
Why are you being so funny?
It's embarrassing.
To all of you who have been watching our young couples channel.
I'm filming this because I feel I owe you an apology again.I'm filming this because I feel I owe you an apology again.
In the video you have just seen
Mirta's act of drinking directly from the yakiniku sauce
I am very sorry that you all know my feelings of disappointment.
I am very sorry for that.
I am deeply sorry that I have hurt the feelings of five young listeners who have subscribed to the Young Couple channel.
We deeply regret our actions, and we will continue to work with Rinka to reach our goal of one million subscribers.
I am very sorry for what I have done.
Mmm.
Is it good?
I love meat!
Basin.
You know, the first time we ever did this.
We had a reunion.
We had yakiniku, right?
Yeah, it was fun.
It was fun.
We talked a lot about that time.
Do you remember what meat I said I liked best?
I remember.
The belly.
No, I was wrong. That's the variety. Variety.
Of course. Variety, variety, variety.
Do you remember? I remember. I remember.
Are you kidding?
No? That's enough.
What's really the right answer?
Samgyeopsal. Samgyeopsal.
Who are you talking about?
Oh, no, no, no, no, no.
I'm sorry, are you mad at me?
Yes, I am.
No, you're mad at me.
Yeah, I am.
No, I'm not mad at you.
I'm so embarrassed. I'm so embarrassed.
I love apples.
Embarrassing.
Okay, bye.
I've eaten a lot and I'm full.
I think I'll close up.
I'm going to continue to bring you exciting
I'll continue to bring you exciting videos from now on.
I'll keep bringing you exciting videos.
Please subscribe to my channel!
I'm so embarrassed... I'm so embarrassed...
Bye bye!
I have an announcement to make to all of you who have been watching our young couples channel!
I have decided to part ways with my girlfriend Buteko.
The reason is that I kept calling her Buteko Buteka!
After talking with Buteko, we have decided to part ways.
I am deleting this channel today.
From now on, I will start my own YouTube channel
I will start my own YouTube channel "Mew to Fishing Zammai" and post on it.
Please subscribe to my channel!
That's all for now!
Yakiniku sauce, please.
LOL!
LOL!LOL!
To all of you who are watching.
Uh, can I speak louder once?
Okay.
Wow.
I'm dying.